Guide to the Robert J. Havighurst Papers 1921-1991
University of Chicago Library
- Series XII: Adulthood, Aging, and the Life Cycle
  - Subseries 1: Human development and the Life Span
    - Dev. Psych Courses (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Dev. Psych-Hunt (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - AERA Life Span (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Life Span Dev and Education (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Education Through the Adult Life Span (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Human Development 412 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Human Development 412 Soc/Class Socialization (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Dev Through the Life Span (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Human Development and Education (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Dominant Concerns in the Life Cycle (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - DT Revision (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Publication-Developmental Tasks and Education (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Development Psychology (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - NACSAP (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - School-Age Parents (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Teenage Parents-Speech (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Teenage Parents-Data and Biblio (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Counseling Adolescent Girls in the 1960s (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Middle School (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Evanston-Middle School (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum A-Current (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Curriculum B-Inquiry (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - 384-Dittos (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Interviews Based on Havighurst’s Developmental Tasks (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Middle Childhood Tasks (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Dev Tasks, Miscellaneous (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Identity (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Develop. Task Study-Intell. Achiev. (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - PT Method (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Develop. Tasks of Middle Childhood (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - The Open and Closed Mind (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Developmental Tasks of Elderly People (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Continuity Paper (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - AAIR (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Human Development 315-Final Examination (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Human Development 312G (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Physical Development-Visual (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - ISSBD-1977-1981 (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - ISSBD-(Old) (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - ISSBD-Ann Arbor Conference (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - ISSBD-Program (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - ISSBD, IAHD (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - IAHD Before 1969 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Phys Ed and Sports (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Human Development in the Science Program (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - HD 310 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Physical Development (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Nurturing the Cognitive Skills in Health (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - 312 G Outlines, etc (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Body Build (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Growth I (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Growth II (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Growth X (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Menopause (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - 312 G-Reserve (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Research Committees (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Life-Span Developmental Psychology (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Argentina Education Data (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - RJH Lectures in Spanish (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Students Values (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Aparecida’s Papers (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Sample (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Aranagura (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Brazil-Education-General (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Scales (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - SES of Studies (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Social Change, Social Mobility (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Latin America (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Youth Statistics Population (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Society and Education, ed RJH (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Brazil (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Cooperative Study School Practices (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Aparecida Papers (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Brazil (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 1 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Rio Favela Study (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Moreira (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Ruscos Draft (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Favela Project (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Brazil (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Ward Rem Study (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Ed and Harris Poll Data (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Reminiscence (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Gugenheim Fellowship (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Cultural Motivation (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Rio (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Maps (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Teachers, Spring (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Survey Report (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Improvement Ideas (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Analysis of San Francisco (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Haydee’s Scale of Employees and Employers (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Social Origin (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Baltimore Demographic Data (1 of 2) (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Baltimore Demographic Data (2 of 2) (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - 312G-Growth, Development, Nutrition (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Human Development 315-Physical Growth Examination (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Physiol. Development in Childhood (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Personality and Physique (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 2: Kansas City Studies
    - Kansas City Material-1983 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - KC-Significant Others (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - KC Project-1956-1963-Disorganization Theory (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Carnegie Corporation-Finances (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - KC Study-Public Relations and Publications (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Kansas City Research (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Reisman (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - KC Plans, 1954-55 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Kansas City Research Plans, 1951-53 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous KC Research Materials (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - M. Loeb Miscellaneous Requests (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - History-Kansas City (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - First Child Health and Human Development (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - OH Research Proposals (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Kansas City Association of Trusts and Foundations (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - KC Congregation (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Dan Levin-KC (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - K-City (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - KC-1966 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - KC Consults (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Kansas City-Levine (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Problems of Integration in the Kansas City Public Schools, 1965 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - KC Desegregation (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - KC Desegregation-Rights (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Problems of Integration in the Kansas City Public Schools, 1965 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - AHLSTROM (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Disruptive Adolescence-Safer (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Safer KC (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Law Enforcement and Community Studies (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Project for Follow Up Study of WLS Boys (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Follow-Up Study (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Jossey-Bass (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Boy Builders of Bloomington, Inc. (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Progress Report Number 3, Work Study Program, Kansas City (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - KC Work Study Programs (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Work Study Progress Report, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - KC Follow Up (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Community Studies (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - A Work Study Program to Reduce Juvenile Delinquency (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - The Second Progress Report of the Work Study Program (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Progress Reports of the Work Study Program (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - KC Higher Ed Project, 1966-8 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Higher Ed Project (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous KC Materials (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Black binder (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Higher Ed Project, KC (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Edna Mitchell (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - 2 SPI (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Kansas City Memos, Irwin Deutcher (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - #1-#7 USPHS (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Serial Role (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Surplus Numbered Schedules (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - KC Invitations to Interviewers (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Interview Forms (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Betty OPR Interviews (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - KC Book (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - KC Safety Adults Study (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Peck’s Chapter (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - LS and Mid-Guide (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Life Style Chapter (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - How to Op KC Study, Sample, Interview (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Field Work Chapter (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - RS Male Interviews-Duplicates (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Margaret Laughrey (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3: Chicago Adult Attitude Study
    - Carnegie Corporation: Community Study of Middle Age and Later Maturity (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Carnegie Corporation: Community Study of Middle Age and Later Maturity-Staff (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Your Activities and Attitudes Sales (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Your Activities and Attitudes (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Your Activities and Attitudes, Manual of Instructions (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Your Activities and Attitudes, Attitude Scores (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - International Committee for Mental Hygiene (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Study of Social Roles (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Kansas City Interviews, Richard P. Coleman (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Activities and Attitudes, Schedule (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Kansas City, Doris Kells (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Coleman Study (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Ch 1 KC Book (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Instruments (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - RJH Interviews-KC-1955 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 4: Gerontology
    - Cross National Study of Adjustment to Retirement (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Leisure (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Social Adjustment to Old Age (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Disengagement Background Material (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Your Activities and Attitudes-Coding Instructions (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Adult Attitudes Scale (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Letters from Old People, 1949 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Proposal for Study of Social Factors Related to Mortality from CV Diseases in Chicago, Jan 1950 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Later Maturity (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Work and Play of Older People (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Gerontological Society-Documentation Committee (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Post-Retirement Activities of Methodist Ministers (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Champaign-Youth on Age (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Demography Pre-1980 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Coping With Health in Aging (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Ross Wetenland-Aging (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Short Papers-RM (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Recreation-Gerontology (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Personal Experience of Aging-Various People (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Economic Security (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - European Gerontology (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Media and Aging (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Foster Grad Parent Project (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Department of Aging Community Core (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Missed Committees (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Oral Histories (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Committee to Protect Social Security (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Ethics and Aging (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - General on Aging (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Elderly, Papers, Etc. (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Minorities and Elderly (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Outlines (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Social Gerontology (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - After 60 Study (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Retired Living-Hyde Park, Kenwood (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Retired Living in Hyde Park (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Housing the Elderly in Chicago (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Senior Centers (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Clark Tibbits, Gerontology Committee (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Poll on Aging with 80s (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Income Development Comm. (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Envelope from Hartigan, IL Attorney General (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Advisory and Aging (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Neil Hartigan-Committees (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Life Satisfaction (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - Middle Aged (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - Middle Adult Study (Box 172, Folder 20)
    - Coping with Health Problems (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 3 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Eugene Friedman (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Validity of the Chicago Attitude as a Measure of Personal Adjustment in Old Age (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - RJH Statistical Profile of Youth (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Global 2000 Report (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Don-Evaluation of Social Security (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Aging and Social Security (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Gerontology (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Encyclopedia of Aging (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Middle Years (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Body, Self and Society (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Buhler, Charlotte, by RJH (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Burgess, Ernest W, by RJH in The Gerontologist, Summer 1968 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Compulsory Retirement at a Fixed Age? (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Disengagement, Personality and Life Satisfaction in the Later Years (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - AERH Paper 1981: Ed Needs of the Elderly in the 1980s (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Elderly as a Minority Group (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - Flexible Work Arrangements for Older Persons (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - Flexible Life Styles and Flexible Retirement (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - Future of Aging and Aged (Box 173, Folder 21)
    - The Future of Cross-National Cooperation in Gerontological Research, June 1966 (Box 173, Folder 22)
    - Gubrian Bank Review (Box 173, Folder 23)
    - Health Problems in Aging (Box 173, Folder 24)
    - History of Developmental Psychology (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - How Does it Feel to Grow Old (Box 173, Folder 26)
    - Leisure in Aging (Box 173, Folder 27)
    - Life-Span (Box 173, Folder 28)
    - Lifelong Learning (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Life after 60 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Life Begins Again at 65 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Life Styles and Free Time Activities of Retired Men (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Social Scientists Lives after 60 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - The Meaning of Leisure (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Leisure and Lifestyle (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - The Meaning of Work and Retirement (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - The Measure of Life Satisfaction (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - The Nature of Disengagement in Later Maturity (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Old Age-An American Problem (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - The Older Person in a Mature Society (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Personality and Patterns of Aging (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Profiles of the Aged According to Social Class (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Peoples’ Attitudes Toward the Roles of Older People (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Public Attitudes Toward Various Role-Activities of Older People (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - How Changes in Later Years Affect the Quality of Life (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Publications in Gerontology (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - The Relative Importance of Social Class and Ethnicity in Human Development (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - The Social Competence of Middle Age People (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - A Social-Psychological Perspective on Aging (Box 174, Folder 21)
    - The Sociologic Meaning of Aging (Box 174, Folder 22)
    - Social Roles, Work, Leisure and Education (Box 174, Folder 23)
    - The State and the Aging Individual (Box 174, Folder 24)
    - Understanding the Elderly and the Aging Process (Box 174, Folder 25)
    - Validity of the Chicago Attitude as a Measure of Personal Adjustment in Old Age (Box 174, Folder 26)
    - The Relation of the State to the Aging Individual (Box 174, Folder 27)
    - Work and Retirement (Box 174, Folder 28)
    - World View of Gerontology (Box 174, Folder 29)
    - Australia (Box 174, Folder 30)
    - Counseling for Flexible Careers after Fifty (Box 174, Folder 31)
    - Funk and Wamalls Article (Box 174, Folder 32)
    - World Book (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - World Book Year Book (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - World Book Year Book, 1976 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - World Book, 1974-5 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - World Book, 1972 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Emerging Ed Research-Old Age (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Harlan’s Interviews with Retired Persons (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Margery Mack (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - RJH Britton (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Interview with Physicians-Gruen (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Princeton Grad Study (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Life Cycle (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - Education of Elderly, Reserve (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Future of Aging-Reserve (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Aging Papers (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Aging 1974 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Adult Day Care, Chicago (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - Long Term Care (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - Nursing Home Papers (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - Podiatric Gerontology (Box 175, Folder 21)
    - Public Policy and Aging (Box 175, Folder 22)
    - National Policy on Aging (Box 175, Folder 23)
    - Zonis-Retirement Study b/w Blue Collar Workers (Box 175, Folder 24)
    - Pre-Retirement Ed. (Box 175, Folder 25)
    - Retirement Policy (Box 175, Folder 26)
    - Retirement Planning (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Rural Aged (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Retirement History Study (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - UBC 1979 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Books-Library (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Exam Questions (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Economics of Aging (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Sex Roles and Aging (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - HD 314 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Sub-Culture of Aging (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Future of Aging (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Functional Age (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Adaptation and Aging (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Age and Intelligence (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Assn, Role Analysis (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Personality and Aging (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Retirement (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Ch 14: Population (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - 30-50 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - OH-50+ (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Adult Education (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - Gerontology (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - Elderly in the Labor Force (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - APA Divide (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Ger Centers of Value (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Requests for Speaking Engagements (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Writing Assignments (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - HD-Student Correspondence (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Indicators (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - REP Data (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Needs Assess (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Ball, Robert M. (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Gerontology (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Challenge of Aging (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - The Future of Aging (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Ed Needs of the Elderly-1980s, ENOA (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Reality of Aging-Oct 1976 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Life Stories (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Life Span Development and Psychology (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Psychology of Aging (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Volunteerism (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Biology of Aging (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Publication Gerontology (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Transparencies-Gerontology (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Tennessee Conference on Abuse of Older Persons (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Gerontology Society of America (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Age and Employment 1977 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Aging and Jobs for Elderly (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Labor and the Older Worker (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Family (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Applications (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - Orfield-Junk (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - D. Tyack (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - Motives for Leisure (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - Old LS Material (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Problems of the Elderly (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Meaningful LS Material (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - RJH and Devries Lifestyles of Retired Men (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - Senior Citizens in Great Cities-The Case of Chicago (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Sloan Report (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Measuring Common Social Roles of Elderly People (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Proposal and Planning-Sloan (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Hartigan (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Urban Elderly Mini Conference (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - RJH (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Senior Citizen Hall of Fame, 1975 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - NIL (Box 179, Folder NIL)
    - AIR Quality of Life, 1981 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Inter-Agency Panel on Adult Life, 1977 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Evaluation of Res. Projects, AOA May 12-16 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Aging (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - Jaycees Project (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - NERA, Current, 1977 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Social Science Research on the Aging, May 1976 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - The National Research Foundation on Aging (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Directory Committee (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Gerontology (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Tapes (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Ger Soc 1984-1985 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Ger Soc 1984-5 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Detroit Met. Data (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Health Series (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Native Health Service Plans (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - German Old Version (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Collection of Archival Material in Gerontology (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Pres Cabinet Building Fund (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Gerontology Society (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - 1979-1980 Gen. Soc. (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - RJH, Archives and History, Early 1980 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Archives-Ger Soc (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Documentation Committee, Gerontology Society (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Georgetown U. Identity and the Life Span (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Gerontology and Geriatrics, Education (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Aging Around the World (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Papers on Aging, Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Aging and Mental Ability (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - White House Conference on Aging (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - ENOH, 1982 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - 1981 Needs Report (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - International Symposium on Research and Evaluation in Social Gerontology (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Ger. Policy (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Ger Soc Policy Activities (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Gerontological Society, Inc.: President (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Gerontological Society-Awards Committee (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Review Committee (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - The Ford Foundation (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Gerontological Society 1960-1963 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Ger Society Awards Committee (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Review Committee (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Gerontology Society Research Committee (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Authors and Papers (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Next Steps for the Gerontological Society in Applied Social Gerontology (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Soc Gerontology Conference, Dec 1964 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Application for Grant-in-Aid, US Public Health Service (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Ger. Soc. Basic Info (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Proposals for Research on Aging (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Meaning of Work (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Appendices (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Cross National Study of Adjustment to Retirement-The Nature of the Research (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - 1965 Application for Cross Culture: Aging (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Form for Presenting Data from Each Country (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - National Research On Aging, Conference, 1963-64 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Current x-national Conference (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Wageningen Conference (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Loza de Garda Conference (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Archives (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Bagnell-Archives Report (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Ger. Soc. (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Archives, 1978-1979, Dallas (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Material for the Archives-Gerontological Society, 1978-1979 (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Ger. Soc. History Project (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Ger. Soc. Archives (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Research-Development, Ger. Society (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Corad Expenses-HD. Pub. Fund (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Research and Development in Social Gerontology (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - CORAD, 1970-1971 (Box 185, Folder 3)